



I've been doing basic website design for 1+ years and want to expand my knowledge in the IT field by building upon my experience in computer servicing, maintaining, and troubleshooting. My motivation in continuing in this field helps me pick up new skills on the job.

Experience

02-2017 - present

IT Specialist

Sunnyside Road Baptist Church

Responsibilities

- Website/Social Media building and maintenance
- Technological expense consulting
- PC maintenance and servicing
- Event Scheduling

11-2017 - present

Sales Associate

Fry's Electronics, Computer Department

Responsibilities

- Being knowledgeable about current technology
- Troubleshooting customer issues with viable solutions for their needs
- Restocking shelves

05-2017 -07-2017 **Summer Missionary**

State Convention of Baptists in Indiana, Highland Lakes Baptist Camp

Responsibilities

- Grounds Maintenance
- Leadership Roles depending on each camp
- Sound Booth Technician
- Mentoring campers spiritually

Education

08-2012 -

Lawrence Central High School

06-2016

- Core 40 Diploma w/ Academic & Technical Honors
- GPA 4.0

Q

Certificates

05-2016

CompTIA A+ Computer Repair

05-2016

TestOut PC Pro

B

Interests

- Music Performance
- Computer Building

Video Creation



Address

8417 Stark Drive Indianapolis, IN 46216

Phone

(317) 495-8720

E-mail

briandoan71@yahoo.com

Date of birth

05-05-1998



Persistent in problem solving

Quick learner on the job

Work well with other

Can be independent in work



Vietnamese

Conversationally Fluent

Spanish

